sourceaudio.com 2016-10-15

# Privacy Policy | SourceAudio

## Our Privacy Policy

(last update: Jan 2011)

This Website (the "Website") is owned and operated by SourceAudio (the "Company"). Company has created this privacy statement in order to demonstrate our firm commitment to our visitors' privacy. The following discloses our information gathering and dissemination practices for sourceaudio.com  
The Website may only be used or otherwise accessed by persons 18 years of age or older. See Terms and Conditions. If we reasonably believe that someone under 18 years of age has provided us with personal information, we will make reasonable efforts to remove such personal information from our database.  
When using the Website, you may be asked to provide certain personal information about you and/or your company, such as name, company name, address, phone number, fax number and e-mail address. This information may be requested when you sign up for an account, request a license agreement or report music usage. In addition to personal/company information, may collect certain demographic information from its users, such as position with company, facility type and buying preferences.  
The Website server automatically collects data about your home server's domain when you visit the Website. For example, if you visit us from your AOL account, our server will record a visit from aol.com. Our server may also record the referring page that linked you to us, e.g., a search engine or your geographical location. We use this information only for internal review in aggregate and non-personally-identifiable form. Our server will not automatically record your name or e-mail address. Your e-mail address and other personally identifying data will not be known to Company unless you voluntarily submit them to us or post them on a bulletin board or chat room.  
The Website also uses "cookies," or text files sent from our server and saved by your web browser to your computer's hard drive. Our cookies are sent back only to our server and cannot be read by other websites' servers. Cookies are not programs and cannot be used to read any data or files on your computer. We use cookies to record how many times a user has visited the Website and what pages the user has accessed, as well as login information.

### Information we gather

The following information is automatically gathered from our website visitors:  
IP address

### How we use the information we gather

We use your personal/company information for various purposes, such as fulfilling orders, responding to requests for information and providing customer assistance. We use demographic information in order to improve our content, product offerings, and promotional and marketing efforts. Company may also use demographic information to create aggregate reports about its users. The demographic information and aggregate reports do not contain any information that could be used to personally identify you.  
In addition, Company reserves the right to disclose any content, records, or electronic communication of any kind (including personal information or private electronic communication transmitted on the Website): (i) to satisfy any law, regulation, or government request; (ii) if such disclosure is necessary or appropriate to operate Company; or (iii) to protect the rights or property of Company or its users, sponsors, providers, licensors, or merchants. Company also reserves the right to reject any order or to request additional information from any customer.

### The people that are given access to this information

Your personal information is accessible by site administrators, marketing and the accounting team.

### The security measures we have in place to protect your personal information

To safeguard your personal information, we use an SSL certificate to encrypt your personal information and provide the best of communication security available while you're transferring information to and from our site over the Internet. We also use Authorize.net for storing and processing all credit card information.  

### Our use of cookies

Our website makes use of cookies which are small digital files that are stored in your web browser that enable us to track your return visits to our website.

Your browser settings may allow you to block these cookies, but we recommend you have them enabled to help us personalise your experience of our website.

### Access, Corrections

If you would like to make sure that the information we do have about you is accurate or if you wish to change your information in our database, just send an e-mail message explaining the correction or change to: [webmaster@sourceaudio.com](mailto:webmaster@sourceaudio.com)
